So, who was it?
所以内鬼是谁
Let's just say it rhymes with "Tina."
我只能说  她的名字和"蒂娜"押韵
- It's you?! - No, it's Rena.
-是你吗  -不  是丽娜
Rena!
丽娜
Is that true?
这是真的吗
I'm not a mole!
我才不是内鬼呢
Tina, how do we know you didn't tell Troop 257 to come here?
蒂娜  万一是你让257团来这儿的呢
This is your family's restaurant.
这不是你家的餐厅吗
yeah, good point.
是啊  有道理
- Yeah! - Hold on a sec.
-对啊  -等等
I found these in Rena's trash!
我在丽娜的垃圾里发现了这个
So? Those are my old soccer cleats.
那又怎样  不就是我的旧足球鞋吗
Well, they fit me perfectly,
我穿刚好合适
and I'm grateful to you!
我要感谢你
This is ridiculous.
这根本是无稽之谈
Tina's obviously trying to frame me.
蒂娜显然是想诬陷我
- Tina?! - No! No, I'm not.
-蒂娜  -不不  我没有
I'm not framing her.
我没诬陷她
Wait, Rena.
等等  丽娜
Rena is the mole!
丽娜真的是内鬼
I was right! I knew it! I knew it was you!
我猜对了  我就知道  我就知道是你